Guide to the Penn State Extension records 01131
Eberly Family Special Collections Library
Penn State Extension records
1892-2016
Eberly Family Special Collections Library
01131
274.69 Linear Feet (276 containers)
Administered by Penn State since 1913, agricultural extension agents have conveyed information about economics, forestry, pesticides, soils, agronomy, family life, and other subjects from the Penn State Experiment Station and School of Agriculture to practicing farmers across Pennsylvania.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection contains university records which are subject to Pennsylvania State University's Retention Schedule. In accordance with University Policies AD35 and AD95, all university personnel records are restricted for 72 years or until the death of the individual
Biographical / Historical
In 1911 Pennsylvania State College president Edwin E. Sparks requested money from the state legislature to begin a system of county agricultural agents to act as conduits of information between the School of Agriculture and Experiment Station and practicing farmers. Not until 1913 did the General Assembly allocate $18,000 for agricultural extension which provided agents in Bradford, Chester, and Lancaster counties, to start. By 1921 sixty-two of the sixty-seven counties had full-time agents. Pennsylvania was one of only six states that had a centralized extension organization independent of local control. The agents provided technical information from the USDA and the experiment station, supervised experimental plantings, judged at local fairs, organized 4H youth clubs, publicized their activities in newspapers, and recruited students for Penn State.
The extension service employed specialists in economics, forestry, pesticides, soils, agronomy, family life, and other subjects. The College of Agriculture administered Pennsylvania Cooperative Extension until 1998 when it was centralized as Penn State Outreach and Cooperative Extension.
Correspondence Courses began in 1892 under the title, Chautauqua Agriculture Course, based on independent reading and local discussion groups. The earliest Penn State correspondence courses were on technical agriculture, animal husbandry, and horticulture (plant science). It enrolled 2,,000 students by 1896, offering sixty lessons in five subject divisions; crop production, livestock production, horticulture and floriculture, dairying, and domestic economy. The aim of the free correspondence program was to provide a better understanding of the underlying principles of farming to practitioners. The courses were open to anyone to study at their own convenience but the College encouraged students to participate in local circles of five to twenty students. In 1898, title was changed to Correspondence Courses in Agriculture. By 1917, there were 5,500 active students. Online courses replaced correspondence courses in the 1990s.
Scope and Contents
The bulk of this collection contains the county extension agents' narrative and statistical annual reports of their activities. Also includes financial records, plans of work for the extension service, USDA publications, correspondence, Neighborhood Youth Corps records, Extension bulletins, and compiled historical information about the program. It includes a large collection of glass and cellulose slides for demonstrations, a slide carousel, several ledgers of correspondence course registrants, audio cassettes, moving image recordings, and framed prints.
Microforms; Moving Image; Photographic; Scrapbooks; Graphic; Cartographic; Audio; Artifacts; Agricultural extension work -- Pennsylvania
- 01: County Reports, 1
  - Adams County
    - Agent Reports, 1917-1960; cuid698; 1 Items (Box 1)
    - Agent Reports, 1961-1983; cuid699; 1 Items (Box 2)
    - Agricultural and Natural Resource Center, undated; cuid700 (Box 191)
    - Anniversary, 50th, 1916-1966; cuid701; 1 Items (Box 173)
    - Annual Reports, 1990; cuid702; 1 Items (Box 173)
      Conditions Governing Access note
      This file is restricted.
    - Annual Reports, 1999-2000 (Box 278)
    - Correspondence, 2009-2011; cuid703 (Box 238)
    - General Information, 1970; cuid697; 1 Items; Audio--Cassette--Standard (Box 163)
    - Plum Pox Project, 2001-2003 (Box 280)
  - Allegheny County
    - Agent Reports, 1914-1965; cuid704; 1 Items (Box 3)
    - Agent Reports, 1966-1975; cuid705; 1 Items (Box 4)
    - Agent Reports, 1978-1980; cuid706; 1 Items (Box 4)
    - Allegheny County, 1988; cuid707; 1 Items (Box 163)
    - Anniversary, 25th and 50th, 1914-1965; cuid708; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Annual Reports, 1988-1991; cuid710; 1 Items (Box 173)
    - Annual Reports, 1994-1997; cuid709; 1 Items (Box 174)
  - Armstrong County
    - Agent Reports, 1921-1940; cuid711; 1 Items (Box 4)
    - Agent Reports, 1941-1965; cuid712; 1 Items (Box 5)
    - Agent Reports, 1967-1975; cuid713; 1 Items (Box 5)
    - Agent Reports, 1978-1980; cuid714; 1 Items (Box 5)
    - Anniversary, 50th, 1916-1966; cuid715; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Annual Reports, 1988-1991; cuid716; 1 Items (Box 173)
    - Minteer, Joseph and Kathleen Summons in Civil Action, 1995 (Box 280)
  - Beaver County
    - Agent Reports, 1915-1960; cuid717; 1 Items (Box 6)
    - Agent Reports, 1961-1980; cuid718; 1 Items (Box 7)
    - Annual Reports, 1988-1991; cuid721; 1 Items (Box 173)
    - Annual Report, 2002 (Box 278)
    - Annual Report, 2005 (Box 277)
  - Bedford County
    - Agent Reports, 1914-1916; cuid722; 1 Items (Box 8)
    - Anniversary, 25th and 50th, 1919-1969; cuid723; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Annual Report, 1990; cuid724; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Annual Reports, 1990-1991; cuid726; 1 Items (Box 173)
    - Annual Report, 1994; cuid725; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Annual Report, 2006 (Box 277)
    - Agent Reports, 1920-1965 (Box 8)
    - Agent Reports, 1967-1975 (Box 8)
  - Berks County
    - Accomplishment Report, 1988; cuid734; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Agent Reports, 1913-1950; cuid727; 1 Items (Box 9)
    - Agent Reports, 1951-1965; cuid728; 1 Items (Box 10)
    - Agent Reports, 1967-1975; cuid729; 1 Items (Box 10)
    - Agent Reports, 1979-1982; cuid730; 1 Items (Box 10)
    - Anniversary, 50th, 1914-1964; cuid731; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Annual Meeting, 71st and 72nd, 1985-1986; cuid732; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Annual Report, 1997; cuid733; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Annual Report, 2006 (Box 277)
    - Correspondence, 2007-2011; cuid735 (Box 238)
    - 4-H Annual Yearbook, 2010 (Box 278)
    - Newsletter, 2000 (Box 278)
    - SE CED Leadership Team Meetings, 2010-2011; cuid736 (Box 240)
  - Berks, Bucks, Chester, Lehigh, Montgomery, Northampton, Schuylkill Counties
    - Accomplishment Report, 1997; cuid761; 1 Items (Box 174)
  - Blair County
    - Agent Reports, 1912-1960; cuid738; 1 Items (Box 11)
    - Agent Reports, 1961-1984; cuid739; 1 Items (Box 12)
    - Annual Reports, 1990-1991; cuid741; 1 Items (Box 173)
    - Annual Reports, 2006 (Box 277)
    - Economic and Social Data Profile, 1984; cuid742; 1 Items (Box 175)
    - Program Reports, 1979-1980; cuid743; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Program Reports, 1985-1986; cuid744; 1 Items (Box 175)
  - Bradford County
    - Agent Reports, 1913-1935; cuid745; 1 Items (Box 12)
    - Agent Reports, 1936-1973; cuid747; 1 Items (Box 13)
    - Agent Reports, 1974-1988; cuid748; 1 Items (Box 14)
    - Annual Report and Calendar of Events, 1993-1997; cuid749; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Annual Reports, 1991; cuid750; 1 Items (Box 173)
    - Annual Reports, 2007 (Box 277)
    - Calendar of Events, 1998-1999 (Box 277)
    - Calendar of Events, 2008 (Box 277)
    - Economic, Agricultural, Environmental and Social Demographic Trends, undated; cuid751; 1 Items (Box 175)
  - Bucks County
    - Agent Reports, 1916-1940; cuid752; 1 Items (Box 14)
    - Agent Reports, 1941-1965; cuid753; 1 Items (Box 15)
    - Agent Reports, 1967-1982; cuid754; 1 Items (Box 15)
    - Anniversary, 50th, 1915-1965; cuid755; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Annual Meeting, 47th, 1963; cuid756; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Annual Report, 1997; cuid757; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Annual Report, 2000 (Box 278)
    - Annual Report, 2004 (Box 278)
    - Annual Report, 2005 (Box 277)
    - Annual Report, 2006 (Box 278)
    - Annual Report, 2009 (Box 277)
    - Annual Report, 2010 (Box 278)
    - Correspondence, 2006-2011; cuid760 (Box 238)
    - Home and Garden Issue, 1981; cuid758; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Home and Garden Issue, 1983; cuid759; 1 Items (Box 174)
  - Butler County
    - Agent Reports, 1912-1915; cuid762; 1 Items (Box 16)
    - Agent Reports, 1916-1950; cuid763; 1 Items (Box 16)
    - Agent Reports, 1951-1965; cuid764; 1 Items (Box 17)
    - Agent Reports, 1967-1980; cuid765; 1 Items (Box 17)
    - Anniversary, 40th, 1952; cuid767; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Annual Reports, 1988-1991; cuid766; 1 Items (Box 173)
    - Annual Report, 2000 (Box 278)
    - Annual Report, 2002 (Box 277)
    - Annual Report, 2005 (Box 277)
    - Annual Report, 2006 (Box 278)
    - Fifty Years of Progress, 1912-1962; cuid768; 1 Items (Box 174)
  - Cambria County
    - Agent Reports, 1915-1960; cuid769; 1 Items (Box 18)
    - Agent Reports, 1961-1984; cuid770; 1 Items (Box 19)
    - Anniversary, Golden, 1915-1965; cuid773; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Annual Report, 1991; cuid772; 1 Items (Box 173)
    - Annual Report, 1992; cuid774; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Annual Report, 2006-2007 (Box 278)
    - Annual Report and Calendar, 1994-1995; cuid775; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Annual Report and Calendar, 1997-1998; cuid776; 1 Items (Box 174)
  - Cameron County
    - Agent Reports, 1922-1950; cuid777; 1 Items (Box 19)
    - Agent Reports, 1951-1983; cuid778; 1 Items (Box 20)
    - Anniversary, Golden, 1921-1971; cuid780; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Royally Rugged, 1976; cuid781; 1 Items (Box 174)
  - Cameron, McKean, Potter Counties
    - Annual Report, 1990; cuid782; 1 Items (Box 173)
    - Annual Report, 2008 (Box 277)
    - Impact Report, 2006-2007 (Box 277)
  - Capital Region
    - Affirmative Action/Civil Rights Annual Report, 1993-1994; cuid783; 1 Items (Box 173)
    - Calendar of Events, 2004 (Box 278)
    - CED Meeting - Cumberland County, 2009; cuid786 (Box 240)
    - CED Retreat, 2009; cuid785 (Box 240)
    - Honoring Traditions, Pioneering Change, 2000 (Box 277)
    - SE CED Leadership Team Meeting - Harrisburg, 2011; cuid787 (Box 240)
    - Strategic Plan, 2004; cuid784 (Box 237)
    - Strategic Plan, 2004 (Box 277)
  - Carbon County
    - Agent Reports, 1917-1940; cuid788; 1 Items (Box 20)
    - Agent Reports, 1941-1988; cuid789; 1 Items (Box 21)
    - Agent Reports, 1982; cuid791; 1 Items (Box 104)
    - Anniversary, 50th, 1917-1967; cuid792; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Annual Reports, 1990-1991; cuid793; 1 Items (Box 173)
    - Annual Report, 1996; cuid794; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Annual Report, 2000 (Box 278)
    - Annual Report, 2007 (Box 277)
  - Centre County
    - Agent Reports, 1917-1950; cuid795; 1 Items (Box 22)
    - Agent Reports, 1951-1981; cuid796; 1 Items (Box 23)
    - Anniversary, 50th, 1917-1967; cuid799; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Annual Reports, 1972-1980; cuid801; 1 Items (Box 163)
    - Annual Reports, 1984-1988; cuid803; 1 Items (Box 163)
    - Annual Reports, 1990-1991; cuid798; 1 Items (Box 173)
    - Annual Report, 1996; cuid800; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Annual Report, 2005 (Box 277)
    - Annual Report, 2007 (Box 277)
  - Chester County
    - Agent Reports, 1913-1960; cuid804; 1 Items (Box 24)
    - Agent Reports, 1961-1965; cuid805; 1 Items (Box 25)
    - Agent Reports, 1967-1982; cuid806; 1 Items (Box 25)
    - Annual Report, 1987; cuid807; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Annual Report, 1991; cuid808; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Annual Report, 2008 (Box 277)
    - Annual Report, 2009-2010 (Box 278)
    - Annual Report/Calendar of Events, 2000-2001 (Box 278)
    - Correspondence, 1995-2010; cuid809 (Box 238)
    - Deana Jak Farms, Inc. and Douglas Howe court case, 2007 (Box 280)
    - SE CED Leadership Team Meeting, 2010; cuid810 (Box 240)
  - Clarion County
    - Agent Reports, 1916-1945; cuid811; 1 Items (Box 25)
    - Agent Reports, 1946-1965; cuid812; 1 Items (Box 26)
    - Agent Reports, 1967-1981; cuid813; 1 Items (Box 26)
    - Anniversary, 25th and 50th, 1916-1966; cuid815; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Annual Meeting, 19th, 1954; cuid816; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Annual Meeting, 2000 (Box 277)
    - Annual Meeting Banquet, 1997 (Box 277)
    - Annual Reports, 1987-1991; cuid814; 1 Items (Box 173)
    - Brochure, undated; cuid817; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Impact Update, 2005 (Box 277)
  - Clearfield County
    - #6: Butchering Demonstration/Walter Simonds Fishing/Frank Bloom/Planting Trees/Boy Scouts Planting Trees/Soil Erosion, etc/, 1946; cuid818; 1 Items; Moving Image--Film--16mm--Positive
    - 40th Anniversary Reel of Events, 1956; cuid819; 1 Items; Moving Image--Film--16mm--Positive
    - 75th Anniversary Photo Exhibit, 32636; cuid824; 3 Items; Photographic--Prints--Black-and-White (Box 183)
    - Agent Reports, 1916-1960; cuid825; 1 Items (Box 27)
    - Agent Reports, 1961-1983; cuid826; 1 Items (Box 28)
    - Anniversary, 50th, 1916-1966; cuid828; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Annual Meeting, 52nd, 1968/10/17; cuid829; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Annual Reports, 1988-1991; cuid830; 1 Items (Box 173)
    - Chicken Barbeque Footage, 1940s; cuid831; 1 Items; Moving Image--Film--16mm--Positive
    - Clearfield County Fair, undated; cuid832; 1 Items; Moving Image--Film--16mm--Positive
    - Fall Scene near New Millport/Bulldozer pushing snow/Shoveling snow/Laurel at Fred Browns/Pulpwood Field Day/Rattlesnake/Chipmunk/Hornet's nest/Ditching demonstration/Mowing pasture/Girls leaving for Erie County Cherry Picking Camp/Free Acts at Fair, undated; cuid833; 1 Items; Moving Image--Film--16mm--Positive
    - Fall Scenes, etc., 1953; cuid834; 1 Items; Moving Image--Film--16mm--Positive
    - 4-H Activities, 1942; cuid820; 1 Items; Moving Image--Film--16mm--Positive
    - 4-H Club Work, 1946; cuid821; 1 Items; Moving Image--Film--16mm--Positive
    - 4-H Newspaper Articles, 1994-1995; cuid822; 1 Items (Box 183)
    - 4-H Photos and Newspaper Articles, 1987-1994; cuid823; 1 Items; Scrapbooks--Mixed (Box 234)
    - Grassland Field Day, 1953; cuid836; 1 Items; Moving Image--Film--16mm--Positive
    - Grassland Field Browncrest Farm Day, 1955/06/14; cuid835; 1 Items; Moving Image--Film--16mm--Positive
    - Herefords at Browns/McKee Pond/Caponizing at Sanborn/Weed Spraying at Richners/County Home-Corn-Weed Control/Pruning Christmas Trees/Spraying Potatoes/Harvesting Peas, etc, 1948; cuid837; 1 Items; Moving Image--Film--16mm--Positive
    - Home Economics, 1942, 1946; cuid841; 1 Items; Moving Image--Film--16mm--Positive
    - Home Economics, 1948; cuid838; 1 Items; Moving Image--Film--16mm--Positive
    - Home Economics, 1950; cuid839; 1 Items; Moving Image--Film--16mm--Positive
    - Home Economics, 1954; cuid840; 1 Items; Moving Image--Film--16mm--Positive
    - Home Economics-Making Coffee and Painting Pottery, 1950s; cuid842; 1 Items; Moving Image--Film--16mm--Positive
    - Home Economics-Picnic, 1950s; cuid843; 1 Items; Moving Image--Film--16mm--Positive
    - Ice Flow/Mrs. Dalley on tractor/Landscaping Wallaceton School/Grassland farming, 1952; cuid844; 1 Items; Moving Image--Film--16mm--Positive
    - Ice Storm/Fire Near Rolling Stone/Natural Pine Growth/Forage Harvester Operation/Forcey's Bull Exerciser, etc., 1951; cuid845; 1 Items; Moving Image--Film--16mm--Positive
    - Lester Smeal Homemade Buckrake/Max Forcey's Field Chopper, etc/, 1947; cuid846; 1 Items; Moving Image--Film--16mm--Positive
    - Newspaper Articles, 1956; cuid847; 1 Items; Scrapbooks--Newspaper Clippings (Box 234)
    - Newspaper Articles, 1959; cuid848; 1 Items; Scrapbooks--Newspaper Clippings (Box 234)
    - Newspaper Articles, 1968-1972; cuid850; 1 Items; Scrapbooks--Newspaper Clippings (Box 233)
    - Newspaper Articles, 1970-1976; cuid851; 1 Items; Scrapbooks--Newspaper Clippings (Box 233)
    - Newspaper Articles, 1976-1985; cuid852; 1 Items; Scrapbooks--Newspaper Clippings (Box 183)
    - Newspaper Articles, 1978; cuid849; 1 Items; Scrapbooks--Newspaper Clippings (Box 233)
    - Newspaper Articles, 1986-1989; cuid853; 2 Items; Scrapbooks--Newspaper Clippings (Box 183)
    - Newspaper Articles, 1990-1991; cuid854; 1 Items; Scrapbooks--Newspaper Clippings (Box 234)
    - Newspaper Articles, 1990-1993; cuid855; 2 Items; Scrapbooks--Newspaper Clippings (Box 183)
    - Newspaper Articles, 1994-1995; cuid856; 1 Items (Box 183)
    - Parade, 1950s; cuid857; 1 Items; Moving Image--Film--16mm--Positive
    - Picnic, 1950s; cuid858; 1 Items; Moving Image--Film--16mm--Positive
    - Planting Trees/Feed Carrier and Waterer/Army Worms at Stone House Farm, etc, 1950; cuid859; 1 Items; Moving Image--Film--16mm--Positive
    - Planting WSME Church and Goffee School, undated; cuid860; 1 Items; Moving Image--Film--16mm--Positive
    - Sesquecentennial Grassland Field Day, 1954; cuid862; 1 Items; Moving Image--Film--16mm--Positive
    - S.V. McKee Pond Building, 1950s; cuid861; 1 Items; Moving Image--Film--16mm--Positive
    - Tree Planting/Coutour Strips/Bill Hughes/Don Conrad/Harvesting Peas/Greenwood Township, 1947; cuid863; 1 Items; Moving Image--Film--16mm--Positive
    - View near New Millport/Model T Transportation/Sandy Orchard/Productive Victory Gardens/Potato Production/Sherwood Poultry Range, 1942; cuid864; 1 Items; Moving Image--Film--16mm--Positive
  - Clinton County
    - Agent Reports, 1917-1930; cuid865; 1 Items (Box 28)
    - Agent Reports, 1931-1965; cuid866; 1 Items (Box 29)
    - Agent Reports, 1967-1969; cuid867; 1 Items (Box 29)
    - Agent Reports, 1970-1981; cuid868; 1 Items (Box 30)
    - Anniversary, 50th, 1917-1967; cuid873; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Annual Reports, 1990-1991; cuid869; 1 Items (Box 173)
    - Annual Report, 1992; cuid870; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Annual Report, 1994; cuid871; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Annual Reports, 1996-1997; cuid872; 1 Items (Box 174)
  - Columbia County
    - Agent Reports, 1915-1916; cuid874; 1 Items (Box 30)
    - Agent Reports, 1921-1950; cuid875; 1 Items (Box 30)
    - Agent Reports, 1951-1965; cuid876; 1 Items (Box 31)
    - Agent Reports, 1967-1988; cuid877; 1 Items (Box 31)
    - Annual Reports, 1990-1991; cuid878; 1 Items (Box 173)
    - Ordinance Amending the Zoning Ordinance of Locust Township, 2001 (Box 280)
  - Crawford County
    - Agent Reports, 1916-1965; cuid879; 1 Items (Box 32)
    - Agent Reports, 1967-1970; cuid880; 1 Items (Box 32)
    - Agent Reports, 1971-1981; cuid881; 1 Items (Box 33)
    - Anniversary, 25th and 50th, 1916-1966; cuid883; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Annual Reports, 1988-1991; cuid882; 1 Items (Box 173)
    - Annual Report, 2005 (Box 278)
    - Annual Report, 2006 (Box 277)
    - Annual Report, 2009 (Box 277)
  - Cumberland County
    - Agent Reports, 1917-1940; cuid884; 1 Items (Box 33)
    - Agent Reports, 1941-1965; cuid885; 1 Items (Box 34)
    - Agent Reports, 1967-1981; cuid886; 1 Items (Box 34)
    - Agent Reports, 1982-1983; cuid887; 1 Items (Box 35)
    - Anniversary, 50th, 1917-1967; cuid888; 1 Items (Box 173)
    - Annual Report, 1982; cuid889; 1 Items (Box 173)
    - Annual Report, 1991; cuid890; 1 Items (Box 173)
    - Annual Reports, 1996-1997; cuid891; 1 Items (Box 173)
    - Annual Report, 1996-1997 (Box 277)
    - Correspondence, 2010; cuid892 (Box 238)
  - Dauphin County
    - Agent Reports, 1917-1960; cuid893; 1 Items (Box 35)
    - Agent Reports, 1961-1965; cuid894; 1 Items (Box 36)
    - Agent Reports, 1967-1983; cuid895; 1 Items (Box 36)
    - Annual Meeting Minutes and Reports, 1961-1969; cuid896; 1 Items (Box 171)
    - Annual Reports, 1917-1991; cuid904; 2 Items (Box 163)
    - Annual Reports, 1932-1955; cuid906; 2 Items (Box 164)
    - Annual Reports, 1947-1958; cuid909; 1 Items; Photographic--Slides--35mm (Box 171)
    - Annual Report, 1997; cuid897; 1 Items (Box 173)
    - Annual Report, 1998-1999 (Box 277)
    - Annual Report, 2006 (Box 278)
    - Annual Report, 2008 (Box 277)
    - Annual Report, 2011 (Box 277)
    - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1970-1971; cuid898; 2 Items (Box 171)
    - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes and Reports, 1974-1977; cuid899; 1 Items (Box 171)
    - Board of Directors Meetings and Reports, 2004-2011; cuid900 (Box 170)
    - Commonwealth of Pennsylvania House of Representatives Citation, 1992; cuid901; 1 Items (Box 171)
    - Cooperative Extension Newsletter, 2004; cuid902 (Box 170)
    - Correspondence, 2009-2011; cuid919 (Box 238)
    - Executive Committee Members and Nominations, 1964-1968; cuid916; 2 Items (Box 171)
    - Farmer, 1920-1928; cuid914; 1 Items (Box 171)
    - Financial Statements and Reports, 1926-1943; cuid917; 1 Items (Box 171)
    - 4-H Fair Program, 2008-2010; cuid903 (Box 170)
    - Newsletters, 2001-2002 (Box 277)
    - Seal of Senate of Pennsylvania - 75th Anniversary, 1992; cuid918; 1 Items (Box 171)
  - Delaware County
    - Agent Reports, 1916-1935; cuid920; 1 Items (Box 36)
    - Agent Reports, 1936-1965; cuid921; 1 Items (Box 37)
    - Agent Reports, 1967-1975; cuid922; 1 Items (Box 37)
    - Agent Reports, 1979-1982; cuid923; 1 Items (Box 37)
    - Annual Report, 2006 (Box 278)
    - Annual Report, 2008 (Box 277)
    - Annual Report, 2010 (Box 278)
    - Correspondence, 2003-2011; cuid927 (Box 238)
    - Extension Service Brochure, undated; cuid925; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - 4-H Center Barn and Rose Tree Hunt Club Building Dedication, 1981; cuid924; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Profile on Government, undated; cuid926; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - SE Region Leadership Team Meeting, 2009; cuid928 (Box 240)
  - DuBois County
    - Agent Reports, 1980-1983; cuid929; 1 Items (Box 104)
  - Elk County
    - Agent Reports, 1921-1965; cuid930; 1 Items (Box 38)
    - Agent Reports, 1967-1972; cuid931; 1 Items (Box 38)
    - Agent Reports, 1973-1975; cuid932; 1 Items (Box 39)
    - Agent Reports, 1976-1978; cuid933; 1 Items (Box 40)
    - Agent Reports, 1979-1983; cuid934; 1 Items (Box 39)
    - Anniversary, 50th, 1921-1970; cuid936; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Annual Meeting, 51st, 1971; cuid937; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Annual Reports, 1990-1991; cuid935; 1 Items (Box 173)
  - Erie County
    - Agent Reports, 1915-1955; cuid938; 1 Items (Box 39)
    - Agent Reports, 1961-1978; cuid939; 1 Items (Box 40)
    - Agent Reports, 1979-1981; cuid941; 1 Items (Box 41)
    - Anniversary, 50th, 1914-1964; cuid943; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Annual Report, 1962; cuid944; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Annual Reports, 1990-1991; cuid942; 1 Items (Box 173)
    - Annual Report, 2006 (Box 278)
    - Summer Tour and Field Days, undated; cuid945; 1 Items (Box 174)
  - Fayette County
    - Agent Reports, 1915-1955; cuid946; 1 Items (Box 41)
    - Agent Reports, 1956-1965; cuid947; 1 Items (Box 42)
    - Agent Reports, 1967-1975; cuid948; 1 Items (Box 42)
    - Annual Reports, 1988-1991; cuid950; 1 Items (Box 173)
    - Annual Report, 1974; cuid951; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Annual Report, 1979; cuid952; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Annual Report, 2000 (Box 278)
    - Annual Report, 2002 (Box 278)
    - Annual Report, 2007 (Box 278)
    - Chiplaskey court case, 1995 (Box 280)
    - Fifty Years, 1915-1965; cuid953; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Report, undated; cuid949; 1 Items (Box 125)
    - Agent Reports, 1978-1980 (Box 42)
  - Forest County
    - Agent Reports, 1920-1950; cuid954; 1 Items (Box 42)
    - Agent Reports, 1951-1965; cuid955; 1 Items (Box 43)
    - Agent Reports, 1967-1981; cuid956; 1 Items (Box 43)
    - Annual Meeting, 46th, 1965; cuid958; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Annual Meeting, 48th, 1967; cuid959; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Annual Meeting, 52nd, 1971; cuid960; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Annual Report, 1985; cuid961; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Annual Reports, 1988-1991; cuid957; 1 Items (Box 173)
    - Annual Report, 2005-2006 (Box 277)
    - Annual Report, 2009-2010 (Box 277)